<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flash Fitness</string>
    <string name="label_app">Group Fit­ness Classes</string>

    <string name="error_connection_offline">No internet connection detected. Please turn it on to access this feature</string>

    <string name="error_fetching_data">There is error in system, Please try it again later...</string>
    <string name="alert">Warning</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="btn_no">No</string>
    <string name="btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel">"Cancel"</string>
    <string name="btn_save">"Save"</string>

    <string name="please_wait">Please Wait...</string>
    <string name="date_hint">Select a date</string>
    <string name="choose_date">Choose Date</string>


    <string name="label_home">News</string>
    <string name="label_schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="label_virtual">Training</string>
    <string name="label_reward">Reward</string>
    <string name="label_profile">Profile</string>

    <integer-array name="posters">
        <item>@drawable/gambar_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_4</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_5</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_6</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_7</item>
        <item>@drawable/gambar_2</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>DNA Insanity</item>
        <item>Fast Fit</item>
        <item>Floating Yoga</item>
        <item>Peloton</item>
        <item>Playground</item>
        <item>Saltar</item>
        <item>Strong By Zumba</item>
        <item>Kettlebell</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="overviews">
        <item>Get crazy on the gym floor with the hottest dance club moves and party your way to a fitter you.</item>
        <item>Get fit and go fast with bodyweight exercises and equipment to up your endurance and burn calories.</item>
        <item>Glow with health and strength when you defy gravity in this low-impact combo of yoga and Pilates.</item>
        <item>Feel the burn of a 3-part spin workout and explore different terrains without even leaving the gym.</item>
        <item>Play your way to a fitter you with functional equipment and cardio exercises for all fitness levels.</item>
        <item>Leap to the stars and strengthen your core in a low-impact trampoline workout.</item>
        <item>Sculpt your legs and core with an intense routine that will keep you burning long after the workout.</item>
        <item>Play your way to a fitter you with functional equipment and cardio exercises for all fitness levels.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="gps_not_active">Current Location Not Obtained, Try Turning on GPS, Exit the Room and Wait a Moment</string>

    <string-array name="deskripsi">
        <item>Calm your mind with high intensity yoga exercises and longer class duration.
            We will challenge your abilities with a combination of more difficult movements and add experience through exploration and search.
            You will be motivated to develop trust, potential and be open to new possibilities.
            You will develop your perception and improve your discipline. You will feel your body stronger, healthier and more flexible.</item>
        <item>Welcome to class with a mix of dance and music. You will dance with the latest dance choreography and new popular music.
            It does not matter if you are not an expert or are already an expert at dancing, we have something for you in this class.
            This exercise will make your heart beat faster and burn your calories. This exercise has been designed to keep sweating while having fun.</item>
        <item>Concentrate your entire body in yoga practice that will improve your mind, body and life.
            This class uses a series of simple yoga movements and there are several elements from Tai Chi and Pilates.
            You will stretch with songs that will help you relax and calm down. Controlled breathing, concentration, and structured movement are very important to create calm.
            This class is a class with a good method of introducing yoga. If you have done yoga before, you will like various poses in this class.
            You will increase the strength of your core and increase your flexibility while reducing your stress levels.
            You will feel a strong body, a sense of well-being and lasting peace after attending class</item>
        <item>Building on the three main elements namely exercise, breathing and meditation, yoga helps unite your mind and body.
            In this class, we will take you through a series of light stretches, postures, and poses, focusing on breathing to calm your mind.
            This exercise can be a truly effective learning process that enables healing, transformation, and empowerment.
            This will allow you to let go of what does not help you or use it for your personal growth.
            You will increase flexibility, increase strength and build your muscles, as well as cardio and circulatory health.
            Leave class with increased energy, vitality, and protection from injury</item>
        <item>It is all about the burn with Core Ex an ab workout that is going to work on churning out a sculpted core.
            Combining low-impact core exercises and creative modifications to keep your muscles guessing,
            you will instantly feel the burn and be one step closer to that sexy, sculpted core.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="add_new_event">Add Schedule</string>
    <string name="select_class">Select Classes</string>
    <string name="select_clock">Select Clock</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select Date</string>
</resources>
